toptieraid.com 2011-11-13

# Privacy Policy | Submit Classifieds

This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information. We collect, use, and share personal information to help the Toptieraid.com work and to keep it safe (details below).

Toptieraid.com offers a number of features which may include a classified ads section and other sections.

**Collection: -** Information posted on Toptieraid.com except your E-Mail Address is publicly available. We collect and store the following personal information:

* E-Mail Address, contact information (only if you create an account with us)

* Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Toptieraid.com and ad data (all through cookies – you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site)

Other information, including users IP address and standard web log information.

Toptieraid.com does store some information in “cookies” on your computer. It does not store any personally identifiable information. If you use a section of our website that requires a login, your login information may be stored in a cookie for the duration of your browser session.

**Use: -** We use users’ personal information to:

 Provide our services

  * resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems
  * encourage safe trading and enforce our policies
  * customize users’ experience, measure interest in our services and inform users about

Services and updates

  * communicate marketing and promotional offers to you
  * Do other things for users as described when we collect the information.

**Disclosure:-**  We don’t sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with:

* Corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to)  
* Service providers who help with our business operations.

If you submit a classified ad all of the information except for your email address will be displayed for everyone to see (including the email address and other contact details you specify in your classified ad description).

If you make use of any section of our website that requires payment (i.e.: premium listings, or paid advertisements) we will collect the information necessary to conduct the transaction and that information may be shared with our vendors, contractors, etc only as necessary to complete the transaction. If you participate in a fraudulent transaction, attempt to, or abuse the services or network resources any and all information we have or can collect may be shared with anyone we feel is necessary to resolve the problem.

Any products and ads listed for sale are from independent parties and you must check directly with them regarding their provide policies.

**Using Information from Toptieraid.com:-** You may use personal information gathered from Toptieraid.com only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn’t agreed to that.

**Access, Modification, and Deletion: -** You can see, modify or erase your ad data (including personal information) by reviewing your posting or account status page (if account has been created).

**Cookies: -** If you login on our site, we store a cookie to save your email and encrypted password while you are logged in. We do not store other personally identifiable information in cookies. We store non-personally identifiable information cookies to save various settings and prevent multiple and spam postings.

**Cookies and our advertisers: -** Advertisers on our website may set cookies and you should refer directly to an advertiser’s website for details on their cookies and privacy policy. Their cookies may be set while you surf our site, by virtue of the advertisement being placed in an iframe.

**General: -** We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next post or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply.
